uncensoredtube.com 2010-03-17

# Free Porn: Privacy Policy

(Effective as of January, 2008) 

We understand that your personal information is private & important. That's why we want you to know how we protect the information you share with us and understand how we protect that information. 

Our business is based around integrity, honesty, and trust. Our values are reflected in our commitment to protect your privacy. 

We will follow the privacy law in your state if that law is different than the policy described in this notice. 

**Our Privacy Pledge**  
To meet our users needs, we gather and maintain many types of information. To preserve your privacy we pledge to: 

  * Collect only the information we need to deliver superior products and services; 
  * Protect against unauthorized access to your data; 
  * Maintain up-to-date privacy notices on our Web sites. 

**Our Online Information Practices**  
We may disclose information to non-affiliated entities when required by law, such as to respond to a subpoena, to prevent fraud, or to comply with an inquiry by a governmental agency. 

**Safeguarding Your Information**  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet state and federal regulations. We regularly update and improve our security standards, procedures, and technology to protect against unauthorized access to your confidential information. Access to information gathered on our Web sites is limited to people who need the information to perform their job responsibilities. 

**Keeping Up-To-Date With Our Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy takes effect January, 2008. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy. You can always review the current privacy policy from the front page of the site, www.uncensoredtube.com, or you can contact us for a copy by writing to:

Uncensored Tube, PO Box 29502 #8595, Las Vegas, Nevada 89126-9502
